Gross, James Additional NLRB Research Files /4166
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- NLRB Inventories: Truman Library-Kennedy Library-George Meany Memorial Archives-Hagley Museum-Johnson Library-Stanley Diary (Eisenhower Library)-New York Times Index-Index to Legal Periodicals-NLRB Press Release List-Release Guide List to 1983.. (Box 8)
  - Special Releases- Beginning with Taft- Hartley Act: R-1 through R-1839, 1947-1960 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - News Clippings- 1960 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - News Clippings and Chronology- 1961 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - News Clippings and Chronology- 1962 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - News Clippings and Chronology- 1963 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - News Clippings and Chronology- 1964 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - News Clippings and MLR/Labor Law Journal, 1949-1977 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- NLRB Materials: Gerald Morgan papers regarding Taft-Hartley; Copies of AFL Executive Committee Minutes; Early Years: New York Times Articles and some original material.. (Box 9)
  - Letters, Correspondence, and Memoranda, 1937-1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Executive Council, A.F.L. Meetings, 1938-1944 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Statement of Theodore R. Iserman before the Committee on Education and Labor (U.S. House of Representatives), 1947 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - H.R. 89, House Concurrent Resolution 6, 11, S. 55, H.R. Committee Print and Provisions and Comments Regarding Proposed Act to Amend and Supplement NLRA, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Herman Conway Associates: Memorandum, Labor elations Attitudes of Key Actors, and Summary and Analysis of Proposed Bills (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Cartoon Expressing the Affects of New Labor Laws (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Reports, Articles, and Papers, 1941-1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Hearings and Report before the Committee on Education and Labor, U.S. Senate, Regarding S. 1958 (74th Congress), 1935-1937 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Draft Reports and Proposals, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Federal Industrial Relations Act, Revised Draft, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Record: Analysis of the Labor- Management Relations Act of 1947 by Charles Halleck of Indiana (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Report on Temporary Strike Legislation by Mr. Hartley, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Conference Committee Print, H.R. 3020 and Conference Report by Mr. Hartley, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - S.1126, Reported by Mr. Taft, 80th Congress 1st Session, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Perkins Interview (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Labor, U.S. House of Representatives, Regarding H.R. 6288 (74th Congress), 1935-1937 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - News Clippings (1947, 1988) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Limits on Technocratization of the Law: The Elimination of the NLRB's Division of Economic Research: Robin Sue Stryker, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - University Law Reviews: UC Berkley, Cardozo, Vanderbilt, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Notes from Research (1988?) (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Misc. Papers, Notes, and Duplicated Files, 1967-1989 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Bills and Propositions on Labor Relation Laws (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Reports and Articles, 1944-1977 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Rengo Papers ('89) and Summary of Multi- Employer Bargaining ('48), 1948-1989 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - News Clippings, 1940-1945 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Note Cards ('88?) and Letter, 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Hearing before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, US Senate, on Nomination of Philip Rodgers to NLRB, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Regulatory Agency Control Through Appointment: The Case of the Eisenhower Administration and the NLRB, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - University Law Review Articles on Taft- Hartley Free Speech and the NLRB, 1952-1955 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Views on Labor- Management Relations of Mr. Murray, Pepper, Neely, and Humphrey; Pursuant to S. Con. Res. 10, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1945-1947 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Footnoted Materials For: Broken Promise: The Subversion of US Labor Relation Policy, 1974-94.. (Box 10)
  - Misc. Notes, Journal Articles, 1953-1956 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1947-1950 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Letters and memoranda, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Appeals, Notes on meetings, and Statements, 1947-1950 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Congressional Reorganization Plan No. 12 of 1950 Report and Hearings (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Records- House and Senate, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Reports and Papers, 1949-1951 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings and Press Releases, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1954-1988 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Hearings on Nominations to NLRB of Boyd Stewart Leedom and Theophil Carl Kammholz, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Decisions of the NLRB, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Notes from Research (1988?) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - University Law Review Journal Articles, 1946-1958 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - University Law Review Journal Articles, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Misc. Articles: Labor Law Journal, Labor- Management Relations, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Congressional Hearings on NLRB Nomination of Guy Farmer and Albert Beeson, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Congressional Records (1970) and Repots (1954)- House and Senate, 1954-1970 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - News Clippings and Press Releases, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Congressional Records- Senate, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Footnoted Materials For: Broken Promise: The Subversion of US Labor Relation Policy, 1974-94.. (Box 11)
  - Notes on Research (1988?) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Supreme Court Reporter: American Communications vs. United Steelworkers of America, NLRB vs. Highland Park, 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - University Law Review Articles on Non- Communist Affidavits, 1948-1951 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1950-1954 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1950-1954 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Letters and memoranda, 1949-1954 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Notes from Research (1988?) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Speeches, Reports, Analysis, and Recommendations, 1951-1954 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Labor Law Journal and University Law Review Articles, 1950-1963 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 1956 Congressional Record- House and Senate (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Supreme Court Reporter, 1951-1958 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1953-1958 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - News Clippings and Press Releases, 1954-1959 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - News Clippings and Press Releases, 1955-1958 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Misc. Reports, notes, Minutes, and Recommendations, 1949-1959 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - NLRB Operations Report in Fiscal Years 1956-1958 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Decisions of the NLRB, 1949-1959 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Decisions of the NLRB, 1953-1958 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous From Hagley, Eisenhower, National Archives, New York Times, Congressional Hearings.. (Box 12)
  - Notes from Research ('88?), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Education and Labor, US House of Representatives, Pursuant to H.R. 115 p.1216-1273, 1448-1487, 1588-1627, 1806-1854, 1963-1975, 2054-2079, 2237- 2309, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Education and Labor, US House of Representatives, Labor- Management Relations, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Education and Labor, US House of Representatives, Pursuant to H.R. 115 P.607-819, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Education and Labor, US House of Representatives, Pursuant to H.R. 115 p.395-605, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Education and Labor, US House of Representatives, Labor- Management Relations P. 147-393, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - News Clippings and Press Releases, 1947-1953 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Record- Senate, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Labor- Management Relations Hearings before the Committee on Education and Labor, US House of Representatives, Pursuant to H.R. 115 p.3819-4175, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Report on Amending the NLRA from Mr. Barden, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - NLRB Report Appendix: Regional Offices '47-'52, 1947-1952 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Reports and Opinions, 1949-1954 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1947-1953 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1947-1952 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1950-1954 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Education and Labor, US House of Representatives, Pursuant to H.R. 115 Part I, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, US Senate, on Taft- Hartley Act Revisions, Part V, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Misc. Reports and Papers, 1949-1953 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1947-1958 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Decisions of the National Labor Relations Board, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Congressional Record- House, Supreme Court Reporter, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Press Releases, 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - News Clippings: NLRB and Red Unions, 1947-1952 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Labor- Management Relations Hearings before the Committee on Education and Labor, US House of Representatives, Pursuant to H.R. 115 p.2388-2533, 2553-2573, 2691-2759, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, US Senate, on Taft- Hartley Act Revisions, Part VI, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Labor- Management Relations Hearings before the Committee on Education and Labor, US House of Representatives, Pursuant to H.R. 115 p.2855-2891, 3163-3215, 3567-3697, 3735-3750, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, US Senate, on Taft- Hartley Act Revisions, Part IV p.2118-2451, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, US Senate, on Taft- Hartley Act Revisions, Part IV p.1741-2177, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, US Senate, on Taft- Hartley Act Revisions, Part III, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, US Senate, on Taft- Hartley Act Revisions, Part II, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, US Senate, on Taft- Hartley Act Revisions, Part I, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Misc. Monthly Labor Report and Notes on Research ('88?), 1951-1988 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - News Clippings: NLRB and Communism/ Red Affidavits, 1947-1949 (Box 12, Folder 26)